과ooh
Yes Meat Day
Yes, sir.
Is it being distributed now?
It's the same as before because there's no change in what they're doing.
It's started.
It's started? It's started.
Yay!
Oh, that's Piko. Pikoro? Piko.
That's the name of the bento. The one you just had? Yes, that's what's called "pikoro men".
I see... they have some left over.
What's wrong? The world isn't free like this.
We have to have some moderation. What are you doing? Hakata...
Hakata... Don't put it down! It's like an offering.
Put it down, fix it, don't put it down... this is probably it... so it doesn't get too hot.
Don't put this in front of him
Well, that's why I'm here...
The person who falls by the side of the road will misunderstand. What?
What? What?
What are you... What? You smash things up and make fun of me!
But if you think about it, you haven't wavered at all since we first met.
We've been like this, destroying things and throwing in inappropriate jokes together.
Yay! Today's pace is especially fast.
Well, that's all for now, let's get on with the show.
Yes! I'm ready.
Yes! So, I'll think about February 9th, too! Let's begin, Master!
Master! Thank you! Shush, shush, shush, shrikeen!
Yes, so February 9th is probably the most famous day of the year... "Meat Day.
That's right. And there's also Meat.
I heard a rumor that it's a day for fashion and clothes? Clothes Day?
There is a day for clothes, but do you know there is another day for clothes?
Another dress day?
I think it's pronounced clothes day.
You mean like happiness?
There are clothes, but there's also wealthy people associated with it.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know, in western Japan, they call that wealthy person "Fuku", don't you? It's not muddled. You know that wealthy man is called "Fuku" over there in western Japan, don't you? It's not muddled.
That's right.
I'd like to play on the word "happiness".
People say "Fuku Fuku Fuku" over there.
It's the day of happiness, and I've been waiting for it.
I look forward to it every year.
Last year, too, I was so happy to be blessed.
By the way, you know that "Blessed" is toxic to organs, skin, blood, and muscles, in whole or in part, right?
Of course.
And the name of that toxic poison...
Tetrodotoxin.
Tetrodotoxin?
Teki, tekki, tetrododockicin.
Tetrodotoxin.
Most food poisoning in Japan is caused by mushrooms or blowfish.
Not oysters.
Most pufferfish accidents are caused by amateurs.
Yes, there is. There's a national exam.
Yes, there's a national exam.
Then, for example...
I brought a blowfish. It's a little scary.
Isn't it like that? That's for sure.
That's for sure.
What do you call it? Blowfish is delicious.
Yes, it is.
What if you could get some? I'd want to eat it.
I'd like to eat it.
I would.
That's why it's okay, right? It's a little poisonous to say.
Is that what you're saying?
I think so.
I just got a line from Mirei saying she's eating blowfish.
What?
Just now?
That's amazing!
What?
That blowfish is a very expensive fish, isn't it?
Yes, sir. I've never had blowfish in a year.
I've never had puffer fish in a year... but I imagine I'd eat it at New Year's, when everyone's together.
Once a year or once every two years, a plate of pufferfish sashimi, thinly sliced, thinly sliced.
You want to see it? What do you want? It's not like we're in a bubble economy.
You eat blowfish? That's nice.
Well, well, well, well...
And, uh...
Here's a quote.
How many of my sketches will be aired this week?
We do this every day, right? I mean, how many will be aired?
Well........
Can I say two more things?
Oh!
Yes.
Probably horse food.
But...
Maybe it's horse food.
You say that every time? Oh, no!
We got this from Cholmoand in Itabashi, Tokyo.
Master.
Alfred Nobel, the Nobel Prize winner.
Oh?
The Nobel Prize is for Alfred Nobel.
Alfred Nobel's enormous legacy.
He wants us to be familiar with such a great thing.
Is that why you're doing it? It's private.
I didn't know that. So, when his legacy runs out, it's over?
I don't know how foundations work, but...
Anyway, this man is a millionaire, like this, from Sweden, Alfred Nobel.
Alfred Nobel. He has dynamite, right?
Explosion! He invented it.
Nowadays, you don't see people using dynamite around here, but in the old days, you know...
When they were building tunnels, they would explode it when they were building the tunnels. When they were building tunnels, they would explode the tunnel and dig a tunnel like that.
I know, I know, I know, right?
Dynamite was so important that the whole world made a fortune with it.
He made millions of dollars.
Nobel Prize, this man said.
He said, based on what I've just told you, you can inherit wealth, but not happiness. Based on what you just told me, you can inherit wealth, but you can't inherit happiness.
There's something to be said for being rich.
I wonder if Mr. Nobel wasn't very happy in the end.
I wonder if it means that he didn't want to share his happiness with his children.
It's sad when it's gone, isn't it?
It's possible. In our case, it's possible we'll be sad because we didn't get our fortune.
Yes, and one more thing.
There's a famous designer, Junko Koshino.
She's a bit... well, a bit like this?
I'm exaggerating a bit. She started with the hair and eyes.
And later, when the hair became unbalanced, it looked a bit picaresque... and, well, the general image is Junko Koshino.
Okay?
If you have just one piece of clothing that fits you and makes you feel comfortable.
You can wear it and feel confident in every situation.
It's clothing day today, right?
Junko Koshino's hair is so weird and interesting.
It's so messed up. It's amazing, isn't it?
I know.
It's like Darth Vedder's, right? It's like a horseshoe. I don't know how she does it.
I want you to tell me how to cut it so that it fits.
Okay, thank you very much. Well, there's a chance I won't have both.
Well, that's that. That's that. It's sad.
I'm sad to hear that.
I'm Mr. Monopoly, the master of shopping, thank you very much.
I'm a genius master, a genius surfer, the most powerful idol of all, Ebichu Chan, the king of all, a master who went to Tokyo Dome City on a blue sky day and went to play.
The roller coaster I hadn't ridden in a while was so powerful and so much fun!
Devils, do you have a favorite attraction at amusement parks? I'm sure the roller coaster at Tokyo Dome City is amazing!
It's like a whirlpool that goes into the building... and it goes like a whirlpool... and it goes like a whirlpool... and it goes like a whirlpool.
I thought he was going to send me a picture.
I'll never be able to ride it... because the Tokyo Dome is right over here.
I don't go to amusement parks very often, but sometimes I go with friends.
I went the day before yesterday and the day before yesterday and the day before yesterday... do you have a favorite attraction?
I like the Harry Potter movies. I've ridden Harry Potter at least twice, no matter how long the wait.
By the way, he's a Harry Potter fan.
By the way, he's Harry Potter.
I feel like I've grown up today. I feel stretched today.
He was stretched.
Doraemon
Let's read the comments!
How about anywhere?
Heated cigarettes... no... no... no... no... no... no... no... no... no...
I often put my heated cigarette in this pocket.
In a gag.
So, by the way, how do you like it? Oh yeah, before that, I love that Harry Potter book.
Yes, I love it. I really love it. I'm probably going to get a little angry if I say that. I've never seen that many Harripottar movies.
It's okay, it's okay. You mean you like the Harpottar attraction? Yes, as a view of the world of attractions. It's fun. Well, well, well, well... But anyway, that's it.
But anyway, it would be nice to be enchanted by Harry Potter, wouldn't it? Yes, that's right. I'd like to try something special. What would you like?
Rictus tempura. Tempura?
Tempura, you should go to a tempura restaurant.
No, no, no. It's called Rictus Tempura.
Tempura?
Tempura.
There's a spell that says, "Laugh your ass off.
Let's try again.
Rictus tempura.
You don't have to ask too many questions, do you?
Magic.
Maybe you should go to magic school.
Sure thing.
Go to Northern Words.
I'm off then.
Well, well, well, well. What is your favorite attraction?
Well, I like Disney, but I like that one. I recently became a fan of Tower of Terror.
The elevator falls down with a crash.
Yay! Yay! For real?
For real? For real?
Why should I pay to do that? I don't get it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.   no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I mean, there's a lot more to it than that... like a carousel... or a revolving run... or a merry-go-round... but why not?
I'm talking about you guys... but... what about coffee cups?
I'm talking about you guys, but what's with the coffee cups? Coffee cups, too... but... they go up a lot.
It's for adults.
That's enough!
Speak for yourself.
I'm actually afraid of heights.
I didn't know I was afraid of heights until I grew up.
Not at all.
Then one day I realized it for the first time.
I get this indescribable feeling
When I go to high places
When I go up to high places, I get this feeling that I can't move, that I can't move.
My muscles become like this, and I can't move forward anymore.
It's a strange thing.
It's like the magic of a patrol roller, like the magic of a patrol ram.
You can't move anymore.
So, you know, there are often TV shows that force people to put things on the screen.
The days when everyone laughed and laughed together are over.
It's really over.
I see.
What's with this atmosphere?
What's going on?
I want to take him with me.
The more you say this, the more I want to pretend.
No, you're right.
I want to go.
Because in the museum, Devil said he hated bugs, and he was fed bugs.
Oh...
Well, that's not so bad.
I've been eaten, so I can't physically do it, so... for example...
No, no, I'll make it a New Year's Eve event, where we ride the Fujikyu without anyone screaming.
Why? That's a year from now, right?
It's too early to plan anything, even for TV.
Sounds fun.
Fujiki, that's the scariest one. No one rides it without screaming.
By the way... if I did...
I'm not going to ride it, but if I did, I'm sure I wouldn't scream.
I'm sure I wouldn't scream if I did. Yeah. - Yeah.
Because when you're really scared like that, you can't speak.
Ahh ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Maybe something like...
Wow, but I'm not good at that.
I wonder if she's listening.
You don't like it? Surprisingly! I've only ridden attractions at Disney. I've never been to Fujikyu.
It's amazing. It's scary. It spins around like this.
No, no, no... do they have a Plus Girl attraction that goes like this? Yes.
Like being suspended in midair.
I heard it spins.
It's like flying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to do a bunchy jump.
What?
I wanna go bungee jumping.
What? Jump?
Call it a jump!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I don't like it that much! I don't like punch jumping! I don't like it!
I can't even look at it! You know that thing I did with Mr. Kamune?
I'm not even allowed to watch!
But at his age, he's able to do it!
I'm not the only one who can go this far...
I can't go this far, can I?
I've been visiting this ramen shop a lot lately.
I always have miso ramen there... and the miso ramen is like this... tonkotsu (pork bone) miso... very good!
It's very good. I like it there by myself.
The owner of the restaurant is in his mid-40s or so, and his father runs the place, but since I go there so often...
I often run into his family coming in and out of the store, and there is a boy in the 5th or 6th grade of elementary school who is probably the owner's son.
The owner's son, a boy in the 5th or 6th grade of elementary school, would come home from some baseball or soccer club, and his father would feed him.
And at first, I thought, "Oh...
I thought, "He's such a big boy. The mother never sees him, even though he talks to her quite often.
And then I happened to overhear their conversation.
And then she said something like, "You go home and do things on your own.
I guessed that his mother had left him for some reason.
And because of that, her son is a really nice guy. And because of that, his son is a very nice guy.
So, he and his father, let's say, the two of them are living together now, and the father is running a ramen shop by himself, and it's a very prosperous store, so a lot of customers come in.
I'm helping him so much.
I was like, "Is he eating miso ramen while crying like that? I look at it like this and think, "I'm such a shit! And then I thought, wow! Thank you for the food! I'll be back! I'll be back!
I'm so proud of you.
Well, you know, life, life, people, you know, there are all kinds of people.
There are all kinds of people in life, or people, you know, in different situations.
That's right.
Even one ramen is like this.
I'm going to make this place my top choice from now on.
Oh! It's so nice!
I'm thinking of going there every day.
Oh! That's nice.
Why do you think we'd become a family?
It's complicated.
I'm probably older than your dad.
I'll be like a daddy-daddy.
And I'd be like a grandpa to him.
From my standpoint.
I'm like, "What the hell?
I'm going to announce the big event in March, the "Great Coming Devil's Reception".
I'd like to make an announcement about this event.
Tickets are on sale now!
Now on sale!
Well, it's like this...
If you come and see this, you will understand how interesting we are.
Is there any other way to announce something like that? And the official goods, which are made-to-order, are on sale now!
The order will be closed by 23:59 on Saturday, February 3.
Shakoshakoshu? What do you call it? It's a "sakosh". It's like a French word.
I know, right? And a hat-like hat mug, a tote bag, a pouch, an Oyama Rock Festival T-shirt, and this.
And here it is. Kanetsushiki cigarettes.
No, no, no, no. No, no, no, no. Axter! Which pose is this cocoon?
What pose? What are you doing?
It's so small, I can't tell. This one?
That's Eva. - That's it! That's it! What's up with this?
She's like a wow... she's like a woman...
I took a lot of different ideas and came up with this one.
I see... so everyone is like an actress... yes... this is like an actress... and this... is like a phone tab... So you're all like actresses? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I know everything... and it's funny. I want to give you a Nobel Prize.
What? For what? Nobel Prize?
I'd like to give you a Nobel Prize for what?
The prize will be awarded until Saturday, the 3rd of February.
The current date is January 24th.
January 24th is the anniversary of the great event that will not be broadcast on TV.
I wonder what it is.
I wonder what it is...
It's one day past 123. You're eating?
It's really no good, really...
But I'll tell you what I mean.
But the truth is... well, you see, I know everything here, so I guess it is... the truth is... it's my birthday...
Thank you very much.
Today is one day past 1, 2, 3
And so, as has become customary, I present to you your birthday present.
What? !
Wait a minute.
Really?
Oh, my God.
Thank you for the Devil's Charge, Mr. Devilchick.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know. What is it?
There you go.
Thank you very much.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
What?
Which way do I open this?
This way?
This way.
Yes, sir.
Oh, my God! It's huge!
What's in it?
Oh, look out!
What do you got in there?
Oh, here. here or there?
Is it a Sasamgha thing?
What?
Here we go.
No.
What? What's this? Here we go.
It's pretty big. It's got a lot of room.
What? What's this? Wait a minute.
What, what, what, what? Wait a minute.
What? Could this be... Oh!
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Oh, my God! La-la-la-la-la-la-la... Sunbullet Night
I'll never, never, never, never let you go
Wow! Wow, that's really it!
This is what Odayu-san is wearing.
Just in case you're interested.
It's really wintery.
Can I have a shot?
Oh, wow! Cute!
It's a Bichita Green.
Here comes Mr. Odayu.
Oh! Blue frost! Blue frost!
What do we do?
We can't seal off the Rainbow Bridge!
Oh!
I know I said that.
That's great!
Oh, I'm so happy!
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, it's so much fun?
Maybe you can take that fluffy thing on and off?
Oh, you can take it off, sure.
Yes, you can!
That's amazing!
So it can be used in spring and winter?
Yes, it can.
Oh, wow!
It's like this. It's like this.
Hey, yes.
And this is
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Oh, sorry.
Wow, wait a minute. Oh, my gosh!
It's heavy!
Oh, my God!
What is it?
Wow! Oh, my God!
Amazing!
Asahi Junmai Daiginjo.
Look at the back, look at the back.
The back?
Wow, amazing!
Look at the face.
Amazing.
Oh, my God! You can do this!
Oh, thank you!
This is a lifetime bottle, right?
Yes, it is.
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
I think it's probably a good bottle.
No, it's true.
It's true.
Wow, wow!
No, no, no.
It's from Okayama.
It's called Asahi rice.
It's a representative rice of Okayama Prefecture!
Fruity and mild.
No, it's not like that. It has a gentle aroma.
Can I have it back?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
The gentle aroma and
The elegant taste spreads together with the gentle aroma.
Yes, sir
Wow, thank you. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is amazing. Who painted this picture? Did you draw it?
It's from a poster. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
That's great!
Drink, please. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Actually, Ebitu has a present for you, too. A present from all of us.
Thank you very much. It's so small. Amazing! So cute!
Aesop's Aesop, isn't it? I went to the forest and picked up acorns.
They're much prettier than acorns.
What's that smell?
What's this?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, toothpaste, toothpaste, a simple gift...
hand balm?
hand balm.
I'm glad you're happy... but here's a special bag!
Aesop. I'm going to be a fashionable guy.
I'm going to become a fashionable guy... like Usopp.
Aesop? Aesop? Aesop? It's popular among young people.
What is this? Is that what it looks like, like a top-of-the-line product? I'd like to try it on my mascari.
Lip balm! Thank you very much.
Oh, man.
I'm a fashionable guy starting today.
I'm sorry, Master, but I'm going to have to make you a fashionable guy first. Don't chase after me.
I'm already intimidated.
Thank you.
Well, well, well.
So... aren't you guys happy about this?
I'm a little happy. Should I look?
Happy birthday, Sapong! Happy birthday! Thank you very much!
I'm 25. I bought a preview of the movie. I'm 25. Buy the preview. Arasawa.
That's terrible. How old are you? I'm 25
I'm glad you're not Mayama san He was pissed off
I'm glad it wasn't Mayama san
Why's Mayama mad at you? He's younger than me
She's got five dead women's milk and calls them "Alaska-servers
I've had middle school classmates celebrate with me
I was celebrated with my junior high school classmates, and they said, "Welcome to the world of Alaska" I was born early, so I'm by far the youngest on my birthday.
So the reality of being in Alaska hit me hard.
Why?
What is this video about?
The live broadcast was over.
You scared me.
No, I'm not.
Oh, I have an announcement. Is it okay? Yes. Thank you very much. It's a very personal matter, but I'd like to announce that on the 4th of February, I will be performing at the 3rd one man show.
The title of the live is "303 in the room" and it's a one-man show. It's called "303 in the room" and it's a one-man show.
The venue is the same place where we did the second one-man show at Brontë in Yokohama. There are still tickets available.
If you are interested, please come and enjoy the show. It's going to be a one-man show that anyone can enjoy no matter when they come.
Please come. Shingo will be there too, right? Yes, he will be there this time. He's going to be a special guest. If you're excited, Damajin will be on stage for the first time, too.
Yes, and there is one more thing... on February 11th, my birthday, I will be performing a solo cover live at a place called Lodz in Yoyogi.
I will be performing at a place called "Loch" in Yoyogi. This is the first time for me to do a solo show, and I am really looking forward to it.
I have invited a special guest, Mr. Attack of the Third Voice, and we will sing together.
He is a frequent guest at Neck Hanai Devil. Mr. Atack is not coming to speak.
He will be here to talk, but he will also sing with us, so please come and visit us at Yoyogi Rocchi.
Thank you very much.
No, no, no, not at all.
It's always Aoshima.
It's Aoshima all the way.
Mr. Muroi!
Muroi-san!
Aoshima!
It was okay. Thank you very much.
A lot of messages, actually.
I'm glad.
I'm telling you. I'm telling you.
Is it true?
I will read it later.
Take your time.
If I open it now, it'll be a bonfire.
Why? It's gone.
It's gone. It's gone. It's gone. It's gone.
What's going on?
What does it mean?
YouTube?
Well, well, well.
How did it turn into a bonfire?
You definitely touched something that made it look like a bonfire.
Did you have an app that looked like a bonfire?
I'm back. I'm back.
Thank you for all the level charges.
Well, not really.
We're almost done with the live streaming.
We'll see you all again next week.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much again today.
Yes, we are done.